feedmyinbox.com 2016-12-07

# RSS and Twitter feed to your inbox. Free real-time email updates for favorite blogs, feeds, and news delivered to your inbox

"Our Commitment to PrivacyYour privacy is extremely important to us. To better protect you, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on every page of this website."

#### Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Feed My Inbox website. On some pages, you can order service and/or make requests. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * First/Last Name
  * Email Address
  * Account Password
  * Billing Address for verification  

#### How We Use Personal Information

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order and to provide fantastic customer service during the term of your service. We do not share this information with outside parties without your permission.

Feed My Inbox owns the data storage, databases and the Feed My Inbox site, you retain all rights to your data. We will also not utilize your data in our databases to compete with you, to advertise or market to your clients, or to contact your clients for any other means of profit.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses, except under the following circumstances:

  * If it becomes necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of the Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.
  * If Feed My Inbox is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Feed My Inbox will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
  * If the owner of a feed or website you are subscribed to confirms their site in the Feed My Inbox account area, they have the right to collect and export your email address and use it ONLY for continuing the service of sending feed updates to you via email.

#### Will you ever share my email address?

Spam sucks. We never sell or rent your personal information. Your email address will only be shared with a third party if required by law or covered in this disclosure.

#### Questions?

Email us at: [support@feedmyinbox.com](mailto:support@feedmyinbox.com)
